https://www.devotea.com/index.php?page=policy

devotea.com : Privacy Policy
Home » Privacy Policy
Earn Free/Reduced Shipping on Orders as Low as $35.00 to USA and Canada!
Read More...New, Improved Free Shipping Offer×Save on any shipping method with any order over just $35.00!*Free Shipping
With some exceptions (see below), when merchandise totals $35.00 or more, we offer a discount applied against your shipping cost on any available shipping method.
For many orders shipping to the continental US, this will provide free, or nearly free, shipping. For bulky and/or very heavy orders, as well as orders shipping to Alaska, Hawaii or Canada, the shipping will be nicely discounted.
Where applicable, currently only on Fedex express, ground, and home delivery services, surcharges for rural and/or residential delivery will be added after the discount is applied.
Free/discounted shipping is available on packages delivered within the USA and Canada for retail customers who place an order through the website.
Free shipping is not available for orders placed by phone or by
mail.
Free or discounted shipping is not available to wholesale customers, however, we do everything we can to keep your shipping costs low.
Charges reflect the actual shipping cost, not a percentage of the sale.
We also avoid shipping multiple boxes whenever possible.
*Exceptions
Any portion of an order paid for by My Rewards points, any discount coupon offer, or any discounted merchandise, will not be included in the order total used to calculate the shipping discount.
If you are a registered customer and you have points available to redeem, please be sure your
total of full price items will exceed $35.00 after your points are redeemed, if you want the best deal on shipping.
CheckoutAdd items to your Cart to enable Checkout!My Cart (0) Your Cart is empty!Log In
Home » Privacy Policy
CheckoutAdd items to your Cart to enable Checkout!My Cart (0) Your Cart is empty!Log In
.
.
Privacy PolicyBackYour privacy is important to us!Our Commitment To Privacy:
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.
The Information We Collect:
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on websites owned by Design In Mind, Inc. (www.mymorningcup.com, www.devotea.com). In these sites, you can order products. The types of personal information collected are:
Your name and address,
Shipping name and address,
Email address,
Phone number,
Credit card information only when ordering on line.
The Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide when placing an order to complete your order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete your order.
We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only for shipping the product. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete your order.
E-mail addresses provided on orders are used to acknowledge orders, and may receive future product announcements from Design In Mind, Inc.. Return addresses (both e-mail and regular mail) on information requests and other inquiries are used to respond to such requests and may be used for future announcements or followup contact. Such addresses are never used for any other purpose and are never shared with or sold to outside parties.
Our Commitment To Data Security:
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure only authorized use of information, all personal data for on-line transactions is collected through a secure server. Our webserver is located in a major national datacenter which maintains the highest levels of electronic and physical security available. All data, except credit card information, for registered customers is permanently retained on this server. Credit card data, and all data for customers who choose to purchase without creating an account, is retained only until you current order has been shipped.
Although we believe internet shopping through our site is secure, we understand that on-line shopping still is not comfortable for some customers. For these customers, we will always happily accept orders by phone or by mail.
How You Can Remove Or Correct Your Information:
If at anytime you wish to correct information we have, or wish to have your information removed from any of our records other than specific records of past sales, you may submit your request in writing via e-mail, fax, or postal mail.
How To Contact Us:
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us using any of the means listed on our "Contact Us" page.
Design In Mind, Inc.
We welcome Design In Mind, Inc.2885 Country Dr  Ste 145St. Paul, MN  55117 USA1-651-483-2070  1-888-906-1159 FAX
Check my orderSite MapPrivacy PolicyReturns & WarrantyWholesale InformationContact Us© 2012-2019 Design In Mind, Inc. All rights reserved.
Quick Ship!
Rooibos (Red Bush)
Eggs-actly!
Cleaning
Cards & Books 50% Off!
Final Sale 75% Off!
What is Tea?
What is Coffee?
FAQ!
How do I shop here?
Must I use a credit card?
What are My Rewards!
Can I check my order online?
Do you ship outside the USA?
Can I ship to another address?
When will my order ship?
Contact Us
New! Free/Reduced Shipping at $35Spend just $35 (or more) and save on any shipping choice!More information >>
